<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<game>
	<title>Sunsear: Avian Combat</title>
	<release-date>August 13, 2021</release-date>
	<website>https://visionbreak.io/title/sunsear-avian-combat/</website>
	<press-can-request-copy>TRUE</press-can-request-copy>

	<platforms>
		<platform>
			<name>Google Play Store</name>
			<link>https://visionbreak.io/title/sunsear-avian-combat/</link>
		</platform>
	</platforms>
	
	<prices>
		<price>
			<currency>USD</currency>
			<value>$0.00</value>
		</price>
	</prices>

	<description>
	Nature fights back! Defeat an empire in this challenging shoot ’em up game. Bring down planes, blow up tanks, and tear apart giant contraptions.

If you are a big fan of arcade shoot ’em ups, this is one you should try. Its minimalist art style will help you focus on protecting your ship and destroying your enemies’ ships.
	</description>
	
	<history>
	The idea originated in 2017 as a good mobile project to develop using the Unity game engine. Taking a gameplay-first approach, I mapped out simple mechanics and playtested them together to see how the game felt. Once we had a good prototype going, I proceeded with the story and characters.
	
	The goal was to use a small game to introduce a shared universe of original stories. The other stories are what led to my choices for the game's location and plot. War against tyrants with extremely powerful weapons was the backdrop of the universe's story, and the protagonist would be an upstart pilot who always has something to say. The game's location idea was then devised and researched. Big stories were happening on other parts of the world, and South America has a massive varity of biomes that would cover many of the standard video game locations.
	
	Development continued, stopped, and re-started, reaching a consistent stride in spring 2020 and wrapping in May 2021. 
	</history>

	<features>
		<feature>Win awesome achievements when you log in to Google Play Games services</feature>
		<feature>Weapon upgrades that will make you feel like a god</feature>
		<feature>A story with a colorful cast of characters</feature>
		<feature>Use powerful lasers and impenetrable shields to get past the most grueling parts of the battlefield</feature>
		<feature>Bosses that are as strange as they are challenging</feature>
		<feature>Banging music that will push you through to the finish line</feature>
	</features>
	
	<trailers>
		<trailer>
			<name>Sunsear Official Trailer</name>
			<youtube>YDqDhlCfMnw</youtube>
		</trailer>
	</trailers>
	
	<credits>
		<credit>
			<person>Kindra Pring</person>
			<role>Artist, Freelancer</role>
			<website>https://twitter.com/kikimakesartv</website>
		</credit>
	</credits>
</game>